<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Valorant - The Ultimate Guide</string>
    <string name="second">Weapons</string>
    <string name="wallpapers">Wallpapers</string>


    <!-- skins desc -->

    <!-- Luxe Collection -->
    <string name="luxeknife">
        This knife has a small profile with classy royal red highlights.\n
        It has a bit of a medieval feel with a leather grip and lots of steel showing.\n
        It has a default pullout animation and default attack animation.
    </string>

    <string name="LuxeGhost">
        This skin has multiple levels each with a unique look.\n
        Most of them start with a white base and then have varied color accents.
        The white starts on the silencer and works to about the halfway point and the accent picks up the rest.
    </string>

    <string name="LuxeVandal">
        Level 1 and 2 have a red/white and blue/white theme, respectively.\n
        Level 3 is a standout with a camouflage color that goes well with a gun that seems to be inspired by the AK-47. \n
        Level 4 is quite unique with a beige and rich gold combination.
    </string>

    <string name="LuxeSpectre">
        Unlike some of its family members, the white in the pattern takes more of a backseat.\n
        Level 1 and 2 are red and blue dominated respectively.\n
        Level 3 has the camouflage but uniquely has a clean silencer.\n
        Level 4 is more dominated by the beige with the deep gold taking a backseat.
    </string>

    <string name="LuxeJudge">
        Interestingly, this Luxe skin currently has no levels unlike its counterparts. \n
        It comes in a bright red and white combination.\n
        The model takes up a lot of your screen, so make sure you are comfortable with having this bright red beast on your hands!
    </string>

    <string name="LuxeOperator">
        This is the Big Red (or blue or gold.)\n
        The Level of theme (starts at the tip of the gun, escapes the barrel, and returns afterward.\n
        Having a standout skin feels right for this gun, as its playmaking ability is high.
    </string>

    <!-- prismCollection-->
    <string name="Prismknife">
        This was one of the first knives to be hyped in the beta.\n
        It has a beautiful blue and purple gradient.\n
        Despite it\'s good looks, it is mostly just a reskin of the default melee and has no special animations.
    </string>

    <string name="PrismGhost">
        One of the more anticipated skins, the blue and purple gradient looks especially good on the silencer.\n
        It will glimmer as you move around the map looking for those headshots.
    </string>

    <string name="PrismPhantom">
        A beautiful blue/purple gradients looks great here.\n
        It matches this gun well as it maintains a stealthy appearance .

    </string>

    <string name="PrismSpectre">
        This skin features a blue/purple gradient that glimmers and shines as you move around.\n
        But don\'t be fooled, it manages to maintain it\'s stealth appearance.
    </string>

    <string name="PrismOperator">
        If you like the blue/purple glimmer of this skin, you\'ll love watching the light reflect off the scope of this gun.\n
        Note that the pattern does not apply to the barrel or even the handle of the gun.
    </string>

    <string name="PrismAres">
        When using this gun, your screen is likely to be shaking around.\n
        This is perfect for this skin, as you will catch a ton of nice effects from the purple/blue gradient.
    </string>

    <!-- Reaver Collection-->
    <string name="ReaverKnife">
        This knife will always be special because it was the first to show that melee skins will have different pullout animations.\n
        It stays with the reaver theme of big and in your face.\n
        A big golden blade with nice purple handles.
    </string>

    <string name="ReaverSheriff">
        As with the other Reaver skins, this one shows that Riot plans to have skins that make heavy modifications to the base model.\n
        With a royal purple and gold color scheme, and tons of point edges...bring some band-aids!
    </string>

    <string name="ReaverVandal">
        This skin has a purple/gold theme with tons of fanged edges.\n
        It has a special ADS reticle as well as some other special features this skin introduced such as player kill animations.
    </string>

    <string name="ReaverOperator">
        This skin has some noticeable changes over the base model.\n
        The Level 1 matches the Reaver\'s purple theme while Level 5 is an evil black/red theme.\n
        The ADS while zoomed is in quite different on this beast.
    </string>

    <!--Prime Collection -->
    <string name="PrimeKnife">
        The first melee introduced that is not a knife.\n A gorgeous golden axe that will surely make you stand out.
    </string>

    <string name="PrimeClassic">
        This skin makes brings some radical changes to the original model.\n
        It has a purple grip and bright silver top.
    </string>

    <string name="PrimeVandal">
        This skin makes heavy modifications to the Vandal.\n
        It has a silver magazine, black stock, and gold highlights.\n
        It also has new sounds and special animations.
    </string>

    <string name="PrimeSpectre">
        Great SMG skin with a royalty theme.
    </string>

    <string name="PrimeGuardian">
        This was one of the first ever Guardian skins added to the game.\n
        It was added on official launch and has a white, purple, and rich gold theme.
    </string>

    <!-- Aristocrate Collection -->
    <string name="AristocratSheriff">
        This skin makes some significant changes to the base model.\n
        It has a space cowboy sort of feel to it that matches the excitement of getting a headshot with it.
    </string>

    <string name="AristocratStinger">
        This was one of the first skins for the Stinger.\n
        Even though the Stinger is sometimes under-appreciated, make no mistake, this skin is gorgeous.\n
        It has clean lines and thoughtful patterns throughout.
    </string>

    <string name="AristocratVandal">
        This skin slims down the base Vandal model to create a sleek weapon.\
        It also has cool are on the magazine that flows with the weapon.
    </string>

    <string name="AristocratBulldog">
        Beautiful skin that mixes a light gold with strong gold highlights.\n
        Fantastic magazine art to help with those burst shots!
    </string>

    <string name="AristocratAres">
        This skin is dominated by the silver metal and accented with light and dark gold.\n
        It feels like a weapon for a king.
    </string>


    <!-- Ranked details-->

    <string name="one"> Right, here\’s a bitesize ‘everything you need to know’ list to kick things off.\n\n
        - Complete 20 Unrated matches to unlock Competitive mode.\n\n
        - There are 8 ranks, 3 tiers each, except the top rank, VALORANT.\n\n
        - You can queue with up to 5-player parties, must be within 2 ranks.\n\n
        - Rank isn’t displayed if competitive matches aren\’t played within 14 days, but your rank doesn\’t decay behind the scenes.
    </string>

    <string name="two">
        To unlock Competitive matchmaking, you\’ll need to complete 20 Unrated matches.\n\n
        Once you\’ve done so, Competitive mode will be available to select from the matchmaking menu, so you\’ll be able to kick off your quest to reach Valorant rank.\n\n

        Before you get ranked, you\’ll need to complete 5 placement matches.\n\n
        Depending on how those matches went and your personal performances within them, you\’ll then be ranked.\n\n
        The game us ually starts people off at a pretty low rank, unless you’re exceptionally good and win all of your placements easily.\n\n

        We go into further detail on playing in a party down below, but it’s worth noting that you can’t initially queue up for ranked matches without everyone having unlocked it.\n
        \nFor example, if someone who enters your ranked party hasn’t unlocked ranked, you won’t be able to queue up at all.
    </string>

    <string name="three">
        To rank up in Valorant, you’ll need to win games. \n\n
        It’s that simple. If you aren\’t winning, you aren\’t going to climb.\n\n Even if you have a bad game, as long as you win, you’ll still gain some ranking points.\n
        Simply put, losses and bad performances will hurt your rank - loss streaks will really hurt your rank, but wins will always go some way to increasing your rank.\n\n
        there are eight levels of rank, each divided into three tiers: Iron, Bronze, Silver, Gold, Platinum, Diamond, Immortal, and Valorant.

        Winning games is the most important factor in gaining rank, and if you perform exceptionally well your rank will climb faster. \n
        As you\’d expect, losing matches and not performing too well will cause you to lose rank.\n\n

        Personal performance will have a greater impact early on, but this’ll decrease in importance when compared to wins over time.\n\n
        What\’s more, competitive measures how \“decisively\” you win or lose, so if you perform well and stomp the team, the game will know and reward you for it!\n\n
        Manage to reach Valorant rank? Well, winning and how decisive your games are won or lost will be the only factor measured.
    </string>
    <string name="four">
        There\'s almost certainly a hidden MMR\/ELO system which matches you with similarly skilled players.\n
        If you win this\'ll go up, and if you lose, it\'ll go down.\n
        Currently when you finish a match you\'ll have no real indication of where you lie on this scale.\n\n
        There\'s no flashy points animation, or a ladder to climb - you simply check your rank beneath your name and hope you\'ve either gone up one, stayed the same, and hopefully not dipped down.\n\n

        If you win multiple in a row with strong performances, expect to go up. As you\'d expect, if you start losing quite a few, you\'ll likely go down.
      </string>
    <string name="five">
         If you\’ve got a group of mates, you can queue with up to a party of 5 people.\n
         However, whoever you party up with must be within 2 ranks (6 tiers) from you.\n
         This is to make sure there isn’t someone who is far, far better than everyone else, basically.\n\n

         Riot also wants to make it clear that if you do queue up with a party, the matchmaking system will take this into account and “automatically optimises your match to favour similar premade sizes on the opposing team”.
     </string>
    <string name="sex">
         Rank inactivity will be tracked.\n If you don\’t play a competitive match within 14 days, then your account will be considered “inactive” and your rank will be hidden.\n\n
         After your first match back in ranked it\’ll be visible again.\n\n
         Riot won\’t decay your rank, it’ll simply hide it until you come back, so don’t fear if you go on holiday for a while - you won’t suddenly go Diamond to Platinum.\n
     </string>
    <string name="seven">
         Rounding off Riot\’s first post on ranked, progression is the main talking point.\n
         It’s currently tinkering with how to “add an element of persistent rank progression that recognises your competitive accomplishments for all ranks outside of just the match rank display.”\n\n

         It\’ll also be interesting to see if there will be a special competitive ruleset like League of Legends or CS:GO.\n
         Will there be a map pool? Will there be a pick and ban phase before each match? We’re excited to find out.\n\n

         Finally, we imagine there will be cosmetic rewards for placing in certain tiers at the end of a season too. \n
         Expect special agent skins, weapon skins, and more.
     </string>


    <!-- Maps details-->
    <string name="havendes">Unlike the other maps available in Valorant, Haven has 3 Spike planting sites.
        \nTherefore, the attacking team has much more opportunities to win the round.</string>
    <string name="splitdes">Split is the only map which has two Spike locations and three main paths.\n
        two on the sides and one in the middle.\n
        Split favours the defensive team because there are only two narrow routes leading to the charge planting spot, making them easier to defend.</string>
    <string name="blinddes">Blind is a unique map in Valorant because it is the only map that has portals.\n
        The latter allow players to quickly move from point A to spot B.\n
        There are two Spike planting sites on Bind map which can be accessed through narrow passages.\n
        these are crucial for both the attacking and defending team.</string>
    <string name="ascentdes">Ascent, which is the newest map in VALORANT, is set in Italy with an “open middle area,” which Riot dubbed a “playground”.
        \nIt looks like abilities will come in extra handy on this map.
    </string>

    <string name="haven">Haven</string>
    <string name="split">Split</string>
    <string name="blind">Bind</string>
    <string name="ascent">Ascent</string>
    <string name="presentation"> Check this map </string>

    <!-- Abilities -->
    <string name="alarmbot">
        EQUIP a covert Alarmbot.\n
        FIRE to deploy a bot that hunts down enemies that get in range.\n
        After reaching its target, the bot explodes, applying Vulnerable.\n
        HOLD EQUIP to recall a deployed bot.
    </string>
    <string name="nanoswarm">
         EQUIP a Nanoswarm grenade. FIRE to throw the grenade.\n
        Upon landing, the Nanoswarm goes covert.\n
        ACTIVATE the Nanoswarm to deploy a damaging swarm of nanobots.
    </string>
    <string name="turret">
        EQUIP a Turret.\n
        FIRE to deploy a turret that fires at enemies in a 180 degree cone.\n
        HOLD EQUIP to recall the deployed turret
    </string>
    <string name="lockdown">
        EQUIP the Lockdown device.\n
        FIRE to deploy the device.\n
        After a long windup, the device Detains all enemies caught in the radius. The device can be destroyed by enemies.
    </string>
    <string name="leer">
        EQUIP an ethereal destructible eye.\n ACTIVATE to cast the eye a short distance forward.\n The eye will Nearsight all enemies who look at it.
    </string>

    <string name="devour">Enemies killed by Reyna leave behind Soul Orbs that last 3 seconds.\n INSTANTLY consume a nearby soul orb, rapidly healing for a short duration.\n
        Health gained through this skill exceeding 100 will decay over time.\n If EMPRESS is active, this skill will automatically cast and not consume the orb.
    </string>

    <string name="Dismiss">
        INSTANTLY consume a nearby soul orb, becoming intangible for a short duration.\n If EMPRESS is active, also become invisible.
    </string>

    <string name="Empress">
        INSTANTLY enter a frenzy, increasing firing speed, equip and reload speed dramatically.\n Scoring a kill renews the duration.
    </string>

    <string name="breachdesc">
        Equip a fusion charge.\n
        Fire the charge to set a slow-acting burst through the wall.\n
        The burst does heavy damage to anyone caught in its area.
    </string>
    <string name="fpoint">
        Equip a blinding charge.\n
        Fire the charge to set a fast-acting burst through the wall.\n
        The charge detonates to blind all players looking at it.
    </string>
    <string name="fline">
        Equip a seismic blast.\n
        Hold Fire to increase the distance. Release to set off the quake, dazing all players in its zone and in a line up to the zone.
    </string>
    <string name="rthunder">
        Equip a seismic charge.\n
        Fire to send a cascading quake through all terrain in a large cone.\n
        The quake dazes and knocks up anyone caught in it.
    </string>
    <string name="Blaze">
        Equip a flame wall.\n
        Fire to create a line of flames that moves forward creating a wall that blocks vision and damages players passing through it.\n
        Hold Fire to bend the wall in the direction of your crosshair.
    </string>
    <string name="Curveball">
        Equip a flare orb that takes a curving path and detonates shortly after throwing, impairing vision.\n
        Fire to curve the flare orb to the left, detonating and blinding any player who sees the orb.\n
        Alternate fire to curve the flare orb to the right.\n
    </string>
    <string name="hothands">
        Equip a fireball. \n
        Fire to throw a fireball that explodes after a set amount of time or upon hitting the ground, creating a lingering fire zone that damages enemies.
    </string>
    <string name="runitback">
        Instantly place a marker at Phoenix\'s location. \n
        While this ability is active, dying or allowing the timer to expire will end this ability and bring Phoenix back to this location with full health.
    </string>
    <string name="cloudburst">
        Instantly throw a projectile that expands into a brief vision cloud on impact with a surface. \n
        Hold the ability key to curve the cloud in the direction of your crosshair.
    </string>
    <string name="updraft">
        Instantly propel Jett high into the air.
    </string>
    <string name="tailwind">
        Instantly propel in the direction she is moving.\n If Jett is standing still, she will propel forward.
    </string>
    <string name="bladestorm">
        Equip a set of highly accurate throwing knives that recharge on an opponent. Fire to throw a single knife at your target.\n Alternative Fire to throw all remaining daggers at your target.
    </string>
    <string name="barrierorb">
        Equip a barrier orb. \nFire places a solid wall. \n
        Alternate fire rotates the targeter.
    </string>
    <string name="sloworb">
        Equip an orb that slows whoever walks on them after being thrown on the ground.
    </string>
    <string name="resurrection">
        Equip a resurrection ability. \n
        Fire with your crosshairs placed over a dead ally to begin resurrecting them.\n
        After a brief channel, the ally will be brought back to life with full health.
    </string>
    <string name="healingorb">
        Equip a healing orb.\n Fire with your crosshairs over a damaged ally to activate a heal-over-time on them.\n
        Alternate fire while Sage is damaged to activate a self heal-over-time.
    </string>
    <string name="shockbolt">
        Equip a bow with shock bolt. \n
        Fire to send the explosive bolt forward detonating upon collision and damaging players nearby. \n
        Hold Fire to extend the range of the projectile. \n
        Alternate Fire to add up to two bounces to this arrow.
    </string>
    <string name="owldrone">
        Equip an owl drone. \n
        Fire to deploy and take control of movement of the drone.\n
        While in control of the drone, Fire to shoot a marking dart. \n
        This dart will reveal the location of any player struck by the dart.
    </string>
    <string name="reconbolt">
        Equip a bow with recon bolt. \n
        Fire to send the bolt forward activating upon collision and revealing the location of nearby enemies caught in the line of sight of the bolt.
        Enemies can destroy this bolt.\n
        Hold Fire to extend the range of the projectile.\n
        Alternate Fire to add up to two bounces to this arrow.
    </string>
    <string name="huntersfury">
        Equip a bow with three long-range, wall-piercing energy blasts. \n
        Fire to release an blast in a line in front of Sova dealing damage and revealing the location of enemies caught in the line. \n
        This ability can be RE-USED up to two more times while the ability timer is active.
    </string>
    <string name="shroudedstep">
        Equip a shadow walk ability and see its range indicator.\n
        Fire to begin a brief channel, then teleport to the marked location.
    </string>
    <string name="paranoia">
        Instantly fire a shadow projectile forward, briefly reducing the vision range of all players it touches.\n
        This projectile can pass straight through walls.
    </string>
    <string name="darkcover">
        Equip a shadow orb and see its range indicator.\n
        Fire to throw the shadow orb to the marked location, creating a long-lasting shadow sphere that blocks vision.\n
        Hold Alternate Fire while targeting to move the marker further away.
        Hold the ability key with targeting to move the market closer.
    </string>
    <string name="dromtheshadows">
        Equip a tactical map.\n
        Fire to begin teleporting to the selected location. While teleporting, Omen will appear as a Shade that can be destroyed by an enemy to cancel his teleport.
    </string>
    <string name="snakebite">
        Equip a chemical launcher. \n
        Fire to launch a canister that shatters upon hitting the floor, creating a lingering chemical zone that damages and slows enemies.
    </string>
    <string name="poisoncloud">
        Equip a gas emitter. Fire to throw the emitter that perpetually remains throughout the round.\n
        Re-use the ability to create a toxic gas cloud at the cost of fuel. \n
        This ability can be re-used more than once and can be picked up to be redeployed.
    </string>
    <string name="toxicscreen">
        Equip a gas emitter launcher.\n
        Fire to deploy a long line of gas emitters.\n
        Re-use the ability to create a tall wall of toxic gas at the cost of fuel.\n
        This ability can be re-used more than once.
    </string>
    <string name="viperspit">
        Equip a chemical sprayer.\n
        Fire to spray a chemical cloud in all directions around Viper, creating a large cloud that reduces the vision range and maximum health of players inside of it.
    </string>
    <string name="incendiary">
        Equip an Incendiary grenade launcher.\n
        Fire to launch a grenade that detonates as it comes to a rest on the floor, creating a lingering fire zone that damages players within the zone.
    </string>
    <string name="stimbeacon">
        Equip a Stim Beacon. \n
        Fire to toss the stim beacon in front of Brimstone. \n
        Upon landing, the stim beacon will create a field that grants players RapidFire.
    </string>
    <string name="skysmoke">
        Equip a tactical map.\n
        Fire to set locations where Brimstone\'s smoke clouds will land. Alternate Fire to confirm, launching long-lasting smoke clouds that block vision in the selected area.
    </string>
    <string name="orbitalstrike">
        Equip a tactical map.\n
        Fire to launch a lingering orbital strike laser at the selected location dealing high damage over-time to players caught in the selected area.
    </string>
    <string name="boombot">
        Equip a Boom Bot. Fire will deploy the bot, causing it to travel in a straight line on the ground, bouncing off walls.\n
        The Boom Bot will lock on to any enemies in its frontal cone and chase them, exploding for heavy damage if it reaches them.
    </string>
    <string name="blastpack">
        Instantly throw a Blast Pack that will stick to surfaces.\n
        Re-use the ability after deployment to detonate, damaging and moving anything hit.\n
        Raze isn\'t damaged by this ability, but will still take fall damage if launched up far enough.
    </string>
    <string name="paintshells">
        Equip a cluster grenade.\n
        Fire to throw the grenade, which does damage and creates sub-munitions, each doing damage to anyone in their range.
    </string>
    <string name="showstopper">
        Raze equips a single-use rocket launcher with the ability to one-shot enemies.\n
        Damage from this ability is consistent throughout the entire blast radius.
    </string>
    <string name="trapwire">
        Equip a trapwire. \n
        Fire to place a destructible and covert tripware at the targeted location, creating a line that spans between the placed location and the wall opposite. \n
        Enemy players who cross a tripwire will be tethered, revealed, and dazed after a short period if they do not destroy the device in time. \n
        This ability can be picked up to be redeployed.
    </string>
    <string name="cybercage">
        Equip a cyber cage.\n Fire to toss the cyber cage in front of Cypher.\n Activate to create a zone that blocks vision and slows enemies who pass through it.
    </string>
    <string name="spycam">
        Equip a spycam.\n
        Fire to place the spycam at the targeted location.\n
        REUSE this ability to take control of the camera\'s view.\n
        While in control of the camera. Fire to shoot a marking dart. \n
        This dart will reveal the location of any player struck by the dart.\n
    </string>
    <string name="neutraltheft">
        Instantly use on a dead enemy player in your crosshairs to reveal the location of all living enemy players.
    </string>

    <!-- -->

    <!-- Classic weapons -->


</resources>